shanghaiexpat.com 2007-10-10

# Privacy Policy :: ShanghaiExpat :: Living and Working in Shanghai

|  |  |   
---  
|  ****

---  
**on Sunday, November 07, 2004 - 06:30 PM CCT - 7302 Reads**  
  
## **Privacy Policy**

**Introduction**  
We take your right to privacy seriously and want you to feel comfortable using our web site.  
This Privacy Policy deals with personally identifiable information (hereafter referred to as "Data") that may be collected by ShanghaiExpat.com on our site. This Policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own or control or persons that are not our employees, agents or otherwise within our control including, but not limited to, the internet service providers that provides users’ access to the site. 

**1\. Collection of Data**

Our registration process requires only a valid e-mail address and a unique user ID and password. Providing us with other information is at your option. Please take note that your user name, e-mail address, or other submissions that you make on this site may contain your real name or other personally identifiable information and, as a result, may appear on this site if so designated in your account options. Like many web sites, we may also automatically receive general information that is contained in our server log files such as your IP address, browser used, date, time and duration of access and cookie information. ShanghaiExpat.com uses this information to monitor, preserve and enhance the functioning and integrity of the system. Information is collected for analysis and statistical purposes, and is used to help diagnose problems with the server and to carry out other administrative tasks, such as assessing what information is of most interest, determining technical design specifications and identifying system performance and/or problem areas. This information is not used in any way that would reveal personal information to external constituencies except as described above.

**2\. Use of Data**

ShanghaiExpat.com may use Data to customize and improve your user experience on this site. ShanghaiExpat.com will take all reasonable actions to prevent the disclosure of your Data to third parties unless (i) otherwise provided for in this Privacy Policy; (ii) we obtain your consent, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out to the sharing of Data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires the interaction with or is provided by a third party; (iv) pursuant to legal process or law enforcement, we are required to disclose your Data; (v) we find that your use of this site violates this Policy, Terms of Service, other usage guidelines or it is deemed reasonably necessary by us to disclose your Data in order to protect our legal rights and/or property; or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party whereby that third party will be able to use the Data in the same manner as ShanghaiExpat.com as set forth in this Policy. In the event you choose to use links that appear on our site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies that appear on those sites.

**3\. Cookies**

Like many web sites, ShanghaiExpat.com may set and use cookies to enhance your user experience, such as to retain your personal settings. Advertisements may appear on our web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer and is then subject to the privacy policy of those parties providing the advertisements. However, the companies serving advertising do not have access to our cookies. These companies usually use non-personally identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to our site.

**4\. Interactive Functions**

A. Chat Rooms: ShanghaiExpat.com does not routinely retain logs or copies of chat rooms; however, information disclosed in these areas is public.  
B. Forum and Classifieds: ShanghaiExpat.com stores the data contained in these sections on its servers and information posted in these areas is public. Data provided by users to open a classifieds ad account is not made public or provided to any third parties except as provided in Paragraph 2.  
C. Personal Message System: The content of Personal Messages (PMs) are not monitored by ShanghaiExpat.com under normal circumstances. ShanghaiExpat.com does retain the content of PMs on its servers until deleted by the users sending and receiving such PMs. Senders of PMs should regard information sent by PMs as potentially public information. Although ShanghaiExpat.com shall not reveal the contents of PMs except as required under Paragraph 2 of this Policy, ShanghaiExpat.com is not responsible for the re-sending, forum posting, or other distribution of the contents of PMs made by recipients of such PMs, whether such recipient was the intended recipient of the content of such PMs.

**5\. Editing or Deleting Your Account Information**

We provide you with the ability to edit the information in your user account information that you provided to us in registration by using your account information page on the site. You may also delete your user account from within your account configuration page or by contacting a site administrator. Content or other data that you may have provided to us and that is not contained within your user account, such as posts that may appear within our forums, may continue to remain on our site at our discretion even though your user account is deleted.

**6\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We will notify you of substantial changes to this Policy either by posting a prominent announcement on our site and/or by sending a message to the e-mail address you have provided to us that is contained within your user settings.

**7\. Privacy Policy Disclaimer**

This Privacy Policy states ShanghaiExpat.com’s standards for maintenance of Data and we will make reasonable efforts to meet them. However, we do not guarantee the effectiveness of these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of Data. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of Data.

**8\. Contact Information**

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact a site administrator.

 |   
**Privacy Policy** | Login/Create an account | 0 Comments  
---  
Comments are owned by their poster. We aren't responsible for their content.  
|   
---  
  
1: commando (606)  
2: stephenylo (558)  
3: CoffeeHawk_0 (490)  
4: anita-piet (334)  
5: tommyboy (320)  
6: pilot (258)  
7: RURALREVOLT (250)  
8: merdy (201)  
9: UncleFatBloke (170)  
10: aabbcc (167)
